(Man) Previously on
"The Mentalist"...
You know what Red John's
trying to do, don't you?
He asked me
if I'm ready to quit.
- How does Jane seem to you?
- I think he's in trouble.
You tortured the guy,
for Christ sakes.
I gave an evil psychopath
justice.
I'm not gonna apologize.
You're fired.
Get outta here right now.
Don't do anything rash.
We can work this out.
We'll fix it.
(Elevator bell dings)
I doubt that.
Let me help you.
♪
(Indistinct conversations)
Thank you.
(Glass clatters)
(Exhales sharply)
Magic, huh?
"Magic"?
Tough business.
Yeah. No, uh, I'm--I'm--
I'm not a magician, no.
No?
No.
You do coin tricks
and you have the look.
What is the look?
Like you're hiding stuff.
I've seen you around,
served you drinks
a couple times.
Yeah, I remember.
Uh, Lorelei, right?
How you doing?
I'm--I'm Patrick.
Hey, Patrick.
So you're not a magician?
No. No, I'm a con man.
I steal from people.
(Gasps) Wow.
You just come right out
and say it--
"I steal from people"--
like, "I sell shoes,"
like it's not a big deal.
Well, it's not a big deal.
If you know what you're doing,
it's very easy.
It's a big deal because
it's wrong to steal from people.
No such thing as wrong.
Really? When did that happen?
Well,
there's legal or illegal,
there's, uh...
happy or sad, rich or poor,
alive or dead,
but there's
no wrong or right.
Stuff just happens, that's all.
One damn thing after another.
Of course there's wrong
or right. You know that.
I killed a man last year.
Turns out he wasn't a man
I wanted to kill. Wrong guy.
Anyway...
now when I recall
shooting him dead...
still feels good.
It's a happy little memory
to cherish,
like Christmas.
Now you're just trying
to shock me, aren't you?
Yes.
Mm-hmm.
You seem like a happy soul,
Lorelei. You happy?
Yes. I am.
Well, that's nice.
Mm-hmm.
What's your secret?
Faith.
Oh, yes.
Yes, I've heard that.
(Chuckles)
Patrick.
This is nice.
Been looking for you.
How you doing? Everything okay?
Well, how you doing, Oscar?
I'm good.
How you doing?
Good. This is, um, Lorelei.
Lorelei.
What are you guys drinking?
Uh, same again for my friends
here. Cognac for me.
This is an amazing man
right here.
Mm.
This man can reach
beyond the veil of death.
Did you know that?
Uh, no. No, we--
we just met, really.
You ever lose someone?
I lost my mother when I was 5.
(Clears throat)
But this man...
he let me talk to her,
and I truly felt
her presence.
She said she loves me.
She's always watching over me.
(Pats back)
Wow.
Well, it's both
a gift and a curse.
Yeah, well...
(Slurps, smacks lips)
I told my father
all about you...
about, uh, what an awesome
spiritual experience it was...
Mm-hmm.
Best 10 grand
I ever spent.
My father--he's a tight bastard.
He says, "10 grand?!
Screw that bitch.
Go get your money back""
(chuckles)
Turns out
my mother's not dead.
She ran off with
her aerobics instructor.
She lives in San Juan,
Puerto Rico. Owns a nail salon.
That explains why she was
so easy to contact, I guess.
(Chuckles)
That's good
you can smile about this.
Here's the thing--
I'm gonna be forgiving.
Give me my money back,
and, uh,
Mervin here is gonna tune you up
a little, that's all.
You, uh... (Sighs)
you mind if I, um...
Give me my money back.
Yeah, um, can I--pass a light.
Um, I don't have it.
I spent it all.
Okay.
Well, Mervin's gonna break
your arms and the legs...
And then when you're walking
again, you'll owe me 50 grand.
(Clatter)
(Oscar) I got it, I got it,
I got it. Go get him.
(Tires screech, car horn honks)
(Car horn honks)
(Siren wailing)
(Grunting)
(Siren whoops)
(Police radio chatter)
(Man) Break it up, you two!
Hands up!
You all right?
(Both grunt)
(Crackle)
♪ The Mentalist 4x24 ♪
The Crimson Hat
An exclusive of web proposed
by " Benjo The Masked Robber ".
(Whistle blows)
So Benjamin does
this thing now
where he kinda scoots forward
on his butt like a penguin.
It's so cute, it's insane.
Yeah.
Oh, wait.
I got a clip on my phone.
Let me find it for you.
Hey, T.
(Chuckles) Hey, Pat.
How ya doin'? Guys.
Hi.
Oh, God.
What did that?
Shotgun from about
6 inches away.
John Doe all the way.
No wallet, no tattoos,
no jewelry, no face.
There's a lot of blood.
He must've been killed
right here.
Robbery?
Well, there's
no foot traffic.
Nothing but offices around here.
It's dead at night.
Well, he must've arrived here
in some kind of vehicle.
There's an interstate ramp
a block away from here.
Our friend could've come
from Oregon.
Give us 20 minutes with him,
and you can bag him.
No hurry. Hey.
Sorry about Jane, by the way.
That's too bad.
Too bad about what?
That he got arrested.
I heard it from some guys
in vice.
He got busted for assault,
fraud, narcotics,
and resisting arrest
in Vegas.
That's terrible.
We should do something.
- Like what?
- I don't know.
Try and talk to him, I guess,
see if he needs help.
It's been six months
since he left.
(Van Pelt) Maybe he's changed.
- No.
But--
I offered him
all the help in the world,
and he turned me down
many times.
He has to want to change.
He has to hit bottom
and know it.
That's recovery 101, right?
I guess.
Well, maybe this is bottom.
It's pretty low, boss.
When he wants help,
he'll ask us.
He knows where we are.
Hey, Pat. Good seeing ya.
Get our John Doe here
on ice quick.
I think he's gonna be
around for a while.
(Keys jangle,
people speaking indistinctly)
Sign that. (Sighs)
(Sighs)
Uh, wh-why am I being released?
I didn't raise bail.
Somebody raised it for you.
Who was that?
I don't have
that information.
Teresa Lisbon is my guess.
Huh? Lisbon?
I don't have
that information.
Okay. You don't have
You can keep that.
Thank you.
(Sniffles)
(Sighs)
(Horn honks)
Oy.
(Hydraulics hiss)
(Hiss)
(Clears throat and sighs)
(Exhales deeply)
(Sighs)
(Blinds rattle)
Boss? Good news, bad news.
(Sighs)
Bad news--
our John Doe's prints
didn't get a match,
so we still have no I.D.
Of course.
Good news--
SAC P.D. caught a homicide
on Pacoima and Third
last night.
Suspect got away,
but they have an eyewitness,
and they recovered
the murder weapon--
a sawed-off shotgun.
Ejected cartridge was
the same make as ours,
and Pacoima and Third is
only ten blocks
from our murder scene.
That's news.
Good news would be better
than that.
It's a lead. (Sighs)
You're right.
SAC P.D., you said?
Uh, who's the detective
on that?
Not sure. Somebody on
Captain Rupert's night shift.
You're right.
It's a good lead,
and I need to get
out of here.
Let's go down in person
and see what they have.
(Sighs)
(Knock on door)
(Inhales deeply)
Uh...
Mm. (Sighs)
Hey.
Surprise.
Yeah.
Lorrie, right?
Lorelei.
Sorry. This was a mistake.
No, no, no, no, no.
Lorelei.
I'm very happy to see you.
Just, uh, been
a little slow today.
It's--it's been
a rough week. (Chuckles)
Yeah, I can imagine.
I brought you
some chicken soup.
For me?
Yeah.
Come in.
Excuse the mess.
How did you know
my address?
The bail bondsman gave it
to me.
How did you know
who the bail bondsman was?
(Chuckles) Oh.
What are you, Columbo here
with the third degree? (Chuckles)
I'm sorry.
Just a little curious.
I knew who he was
because I was the one
that put up the money
for your bail.
That's a lot of money.
I'll--I'll pay you back
as soon as I can.
Figured you were good
for it.
Why'd you do that for me?
(Inhales deeply)
You seemed like a good man
who lost his way.
I could help, so I did...
and at this point,
a straight up "thank you"
would be okay.
Thank you.
There's, uh, a lot
of good men out there...
(Opens lid)
(Lid clatters)
who have lost their way.
Wow. You're gonna make me
say it out loud?
(Chuckles)
I felt like we got along
pretty good.
I felt like there was
some kind of...
weird connection there
between us.
I trusted my feelings.
Damn it. Was I wrong?
No.
You weren't wrong.
Okay then.
I have to warn you,
Lorelei, um,
I'm not the great catch
you might think I am from...
first impressions.
That's okay. Neither am I.
Bean, tell these people
what you saw.
I'm collecting cans on Third,
right next to the park
where they sell their drugs.
There's a gunshot. Boom!
Then a tall, young,
Latin gentleman
come running out of the park
holding a sawed-off shotgun.
He trips and falls over.
(Chuckles)
Drops the gun.
Then he gets up and runs away,
leaves the gun,
and that's what I saw.
The tall,
young, Latin gentleman--
did you get a good look
at him?
Come right by me.
Got a scar on his face
right here,
little chin beard...
Mm-hmm.
Big gold earring
like a pirate,
black T-shirt, jeans...
(Scoffs) White shoes.
Anything on the T-shirt?
Logo? Numbers?
Don't think so.
Thanks, Bean.
Wait. Close your eyes
and picture him.
Now imagine him coming
toward you.
Oh!
There's a little dog
right here on his shirt.
Not a cute dog.
Like, you know...
(Deep voice)
a snarling dog.
Like a bulldog or a wolf?
Wolf!
Grape Street Lobos wear
black shirts
with a wolf on 'em.
Thank you, Miss Bean.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, so it's kind of thin,
but my guys'll check out
the Lobos,
and we'll let you know.
Well, we can check 'em out
for you, if you'd like.
CBI gang unit has
a really good database.
That's okay, girls.
Thanks, but we don't even know
if it's the same gun as yours.
It probably isn't.
Yeah, okay, Rupe.
It was good seeing ya.
Yeah.
Talk to the gang unit.
See what they know
about the Lobos.
Okay.
I'm gonna take
some personal time.
You take the car.
I'm gonna walk.
Walk?
(Elevator bell dings)
I mean... okay.
See ya tomorrow.
(Grunting)
♪
Oh.
(Man) The zebra's kick saves
its life.
Ohh.
(Chuckles) She got away.
(Roars)
A neck bite finally subdues
her prey.
(Gasps)
The yearly wildebeest migration...
Mm.
You okay?
Brings several months' supply
of regular meals.
♪
(Inhales deeply)
(Sizzling)
(Bottle clatters)
Good morning.
(Chuckles)
Good morning, sleepy lover.
(Sighs)
Mm.
You must have slept
12 hours.
Yeah, I think I was tired.
Mm-hmm.
I gotta go to work.
I made some eggs.
How did you know
I love eggs?
(Smacks lips and sniffles)
(Chuckles)
This is delicious.
Thank you.
We had fun, huh?
Yeah.
Perhaps we can see
each other again.
That's not up to me.
Oh, you have no say in it?
None at all.
(Cup clatters)
It's very restful.
I don't follow you.
I do what Red John
tells me to do.
(Lowered voice) What?
Your freedom,
our night together--
that was a gift from him.
You can hurt me,
if you'd like.
No, I don't want
to hurt you.
I've given up.
He knows that.
What does he want from me?
He doesn't want anything
from you.
After all these years,
he's come to see you
as an old comrade
rather than an enemy.
He hopes you'll come to feel
the same way.
A comrade.
Patrick...
look at yourself.
You need a new life.
He can give that to you.
You have to leave.
He's offering the hand
of friendship.
If you refuse him,
he'll be upset.
Anyone would be.
Get out.
(Sighs)
You know where to find me.
(Breathing heavily)
(Indistinct conversations)
Hey, Grace, you seen Lisbon?
She had to take
some personal time.
- Where'd she go?
- Didn't say.
We have a lead.
I just got this
from the gang unit.
Kevin Cintron,
A.K.A. Purple,
affiliated with
the Grape Street Lobos.
Matches the witness description
exactly.
Did you show the witness
the photo?
I do that, and we have to go
through SAC P.D. homicide,
and they'll want to take
the bust, and we need the bust.
Must be a thousand bad guys
with gold earrings, beards,
and scars.
I got an address
from his P.O.
Well, after killing
two people,
that's probably not
where he's at.
It's a good place to start,
though, and I'm going.
You want me to get you
some doughnuts while I'm out?
(Bell tolling)
(Inhales deeply and sighs)
(Nasal voice) This is God.
(Gasps)
What is it now? (Laughing)
You scared the life out
of me. (Sighs)
(Normal voice) I crawled all
the way on my hands and knees
from that door,
but it was worth it.
What are you doing here?
It's good to see you.
How have you been?
(Lowered voice)
Worried sick is how I've been,
and then you pop in here
like some sort of a lunatic,
playing games,
asking me how I've been.
- Just...
- Shame on you.
stay calm, okay?
It's important that
no one sees us together.
(Sighs)
Why not?
I'm faking my breakdown.
It's a ruse to trap
Red John.
You son of a bitch.
Okay, we are in a church.
Uh, wait, so how does
faking a breakdown--
if that's what you're
really doing,
because it looks
pretty real to me,
how does that trap
Red John?
What does Red John want
from me?
What did he send
that little girl to ask me?
Do you give up?
Exactly, and I do give up.
I quit.
I burn the Red John files.
I freak out at the boss.
I admit defeat,
and I sink
into a terrible depression.
Brilliant. You did
that part great. Now what?
And why doesn't he just
kill me?
Because it's too easy.
He wants to turn me.
He wants to make me
his disciple.
So I admit defeat,
and then he reaches out
to start a conversation.
(Sighs) Well,
that's all supposition.
- He's not gonna--
- He already has reached out.
He sent me a message.
I need to start a new life,
and he can help me.
Help you?
He wants to help you?
- Yeah.
- What are you gonna do?
Well, I'm gonna take him up
on the offer.
I'm in a lot
of real trouble.
(Sighs)
I do need a new life.
Yes, you do.
That's what makes
the gag work.
Then what?
Well, I don't know.
I let him lead.
That's the beauty of it.
He thinks I'm the fish
and he's the fisherman.
Unless he sees the truth.
I am giving him
his heart's desire.
He will see
what he wants to see.
Or not.
Fooled you. I can fool him.
Yeah, you fooled me
all right. Well done.
Yeah. Well...
I'm sorry.
I tried calling.
I tried calling you
hundreds of times,
begging you to talk to me,
begging you to get help.
(Voice breaks) Not a reply.
Not a word. Not a text.
Sorry.
You know what?
I have not been sleeping.
I've been--
forget it. Never mind.
Y-you know, you're a jerk.
And your plan? It's stupid.
It's not even a plan.
But you will help me?
What am I supposed to say, no?
God, you're despicable.
(Sighs)
Take this. It's clean.
I'll call you on it
when the time comes.
In the meantime,
do not contact me.
Do not let anyone
from CBI contact me,
and don't tell anyone
the truth.
Not a soul.
I cannot believe
you didn't tell me
you were doing this,
that you couldn't trust me
with a secret like that.
We're supposed to be
partners.
God knows,
I am happy you're back.
It is a huge relief,
but what you did,
frankly, was a betrayal.
God, I hate you, Jane.
I hate you!
We have your prints
on the shotgun, Kevin.
We have an eyewitness
who saw you
shoot Dashawn Willits
with that shotgun.
I'm showing them the gun
because I'm trying
to sell it to 'em.
Fool tried to take the gun
from me.
I had no other choice.
But the first shooting,
though,
the white John Doe
on Lincoln Avenue,
did that guy try to steal
your gun, too?
I didn't touch that man,
all right? He killed himself.
I swear to God.
Me and my boy Manfredo,
we cruisin' down
the alleyway.
We lookin' for open windows,
to be honest with you,
see this guy sittin' up
against the wall,
got a bicycle next to him
and a sawed-off shotgun.
Just as we start
to get close... (Chuckles)
Damn if he don't blow off
his head.
Hara-kiri.
No messing around.
How do we know
you're telling the truth?
You don't.
You just know what is.
(Chuckles) Come on, man,
you guys ask Manfredo,
he gonna tell you
the same thing.
Yeah.
Man just shot himself.
Boom! Freaked me out.
I wanted the gun,
but Kevin took it.
I got the bike.
Sweet fixie.
Where's the bike, Manfredo?
Got stolen.
(Sighs)
I know. Ironic, right?
Did you take anything else
from him?
We looked.
He had nothing on him.
I think he's telling
the truth.
Cintron admitted
to the second killing,
no problem.
Why would he lie about
this one?
Looks like we'll never know
who he was. Poor soul.
Mm.
(Door opens)
Lisbon, a word?
Yeah.
Uh, is that the John Doe case
you're working on?
Yes, sir. It looks to be
a suicide. (Sighs)
Oh, good. Excellent.
Get that off the books, eh?
Um...
(Snaps fingers)
I wanted to talk
to you about Jane.
It's been six months
since he's gone.
I think it's time
for a little outreach.
Mm?
Well, it's the humane thing to do.
He was a big part
of the CBI family, after all.
I suppose, but I--
I just--I-I just want
to give him a call, see if,
you know, I can't
persuade him into rehab
or a psychiatry program
or some such.
You know, it could make
a big difference
in his sentencing.
He could get
community service.
He could come back
and work for us eventually.
God knows, we need him,
closure rates being
what they are right now--
low.
Yes, sir, and we will do
our best to fix that,
but I don't think
we can help Jane.
Besides, y--
he's made his bed.
I don't think I could work
with him again.
I need someone
I can rely on.
I'm surprised.
I thought you would want
to help him.
Well, I do.
It's not how it looks.
I just have a feeling
Jane's better off
left alone right now.
Okay.
It was just a thought.
(Exhales deeply) Mm.
I've been, um,
I've been thinking about
what you said
about your friend.
Yes.
You said that he could
help me start a new life.
Mm-hmm.
What does that mean
exactly?
A new identity. Money.
A place to live.
A job, if you want one.
And I-I do what
in exchange?
Accept his friendship.
It's that easy?
Sure.
Uh, he'll want to speak
to you first,
make sure you're on the level,
if that's all right.
Yeah.
And you'll need
to bring him a gift
to show your respect
for him.
What kind of gift?
Well, Teresa Lisbon's dead body
would be the perfect thing.
(Laughs)
That's absurd.
What did you tell me?
There is no right or wrong.
There's just stuff
that happens.
No, no. There--there--
there has to be something else.
(Sighs)
I can't think of anything else
that would please him.
I can't do that.
I understand
you're not there yet,
but look at it
from his point of view.
How else will he know
you've truly had
a change of heart?
(Elevator bell dings)
Jane.
Not now.
Uh, I'm glad to see that...
(Van Pelt) Jane.
Jane.
Well, it's good to see you all.
How are you?
Uh, we're good.
Never better. Never better.
Jane?
There you are.
(Panting)
Good luck, Teresa.
(Cocks gun)
Love you.
(Gunshots)
(Panting) What happened?
Patrick Jane.
He took Lisbon.
Is he--ohh.
(Whispers) Ohh.
(Voice breaks) Wh-who--
who is th--who is that?
(Panting) It's Rigsby.
It's Wayne Rigsby.
(Police radio chatter)
Ohh.
(Indistinct conversations)
Turn it up.
(Tray clatters)
...in a macabre twist,
after killing Agent Rigsby,
34-year-old father
of a baby boy,
the suspect, Patrick Jane,
took Agent Teresa Lisbon,
presumed dead,
away with him when he escaped.
Authorities will not speculate
as to why he wants
her dead body.
Ohh. I'm hungry. I'm going
to the store for nachos.
You guys want anything?
They got pizza, hot dogs.
I'm good.
Me, too. Uh, Rigsby--
Yeah, I know, I know.
Don't call Sarah. I know.
It's killing me, though. (Sighs)
She must be freaking out.
Well, look
at the bright side.
Think of how happy
she's gonna be
when you come back to life.
Huh. (Sighs)
(Latches click)
So where'd you find
this place?
The owner owes me poker money
he'll never pay back.
Oh.
So that thing you said
before you shot me--
uh, what did you mean?
What did I say?
I was kinda hyped up.
Oh, boy. Me, too.
I thought at any moment
we were gonna get found out.
Mm.
(Cell phone rings)
It's her.
Hello?
Spoke to my friend.
He wants to meet with you.
2369 Foxglove Parkway,
southwest Las Vegas.
Go there at 3:00 today
and wait for instructions.
2369 Foxglove Parkway
at 3:00.
Don't forget the gift.
I have it right here.
Don't bring the whole thing.
Just the head.
Okay.
(Inhales deeply)
(Snaps shut)
(Taps phone)
So you want the good news
or the bad news first?
You lost two fine agents.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
I knew Jane was wrong
somehow,
but I certainly never
expected this.
Well, nobody did.
We received no evaluation that
indicated danger of this sort.
CBI is in no way liable.
Hmm.
Well, the question remains,
why did Jane do this?
Orders from Red John?
If so, why now? Why Lisbon?
I was talking with Lisbon.
I suggested we reach out
to try and help Jane
because he was in trouble,
and she said "no" very firmly.
She said,
"it's not how it looks."
Meaning what?
I don't know.
I don't know what to think.
(Van Pelt) Pretty much
the whole neighborhood is
in foreclosure.
There's hardly anyone there.
It's like a ghost town.
Smart move by Red John.
Tough to set up any kind
of surveillance in advance.
Any movement's gonna be
conspicuous.
He must be suspicious.
No, he's just cautious.
And he's hooked. He believes.
How can you be sure?
Because he wants to believe.
We're doing this thing,
so let's just do it.
Is everybody clear on the plan?
We're gonna move soon.
(Rigsby) Yeah.
Hey, you guys, listen,
I want to apologize
for deceiving you...
(Scoffs) Whatever.
And thank you
for helping me now.
We're helping the boss.
Yeah. She's helping you.
We're helping her.
Guys, cut him some slack.
Oh. Yay, team.
A 12. Rigsby, W.
(Drawer rattles)
No face.
Right.
Could be anybody.
Well, it says "Rigsby" here.
No mistake.
Do you have a tape measure?
Sure.
Bill, I need you to find out
A.S.A.P.
where Kimball Cho
and Grace Van Pelt are located.
Yeah, right now.
Hold on one second.
Put that at the top
of his head.
5'11".
This isn't Wayne Rigsby.
Yeah. Find out where they are.
Thanks. And, Bill?
I want arrest warrants prepped
for every single member
of that CBI team,
dead or alive.
(Turns off engine)
Mm.
The game begins.
(Patrick) Hey, Lisbon.
Must have been a while since
you rode on the handlebars
of a man's bike.
Ha ha.
It's kind of romantic.
Wind in your hair.
You're a sick man.
5-0-5-9.
5-0-6-5. 5-0-6-5...
Uh, there is no 5-0-7-1.
(Gravel scrapes)
There's nothing.
It's just desert.
There's no one here.
Hang on.
Long black limousine.
We're moving in. We'll be
on the scene in three minutes.
Stay healthy till then.
Wait.
Let's just be sure.
(Brakes squeal)
Large man with a gun...
Red John's girl. This is it.
All right, we're moving in.
(Starts engine, shifts gears)
(Tires peal)
(Tires screech)
FBI. Turn off the car
and show me your hands.
- FBI! Nobody move!
- CBI! Don't shoot! We're CBI agents!
You're making a terrible mistake.
Get out.
We're in the middle
of an operation.
(Grunts)
(Man) FBI!
Turn off the car
and show me your hands!
- Hi.
- Hey.
That the gift?
Red John in there?
Mm-hmm.
He's looking forward
to speaking with you.
You know, Patrick,
there's a childish hopefulness
about you that is
really quite adorable.
Put it on the hood.
So what is it, a football?
A cabbage?
Melon. Honeydew.
Organic.
Adorable.
Frisk him, then beat him...
a little.
(Clatters)
Uhh!
Well, well, well.
Agent, this is a mistake.
Agent Darcy, you don't understand.
Please, listen to me.
No, I don't understand.
You're supposed to be dead,
as are you.
This is very strange.
Susan, I am begging you.
Please listen to what
I'm saying.
Our fake deaths were a ruse
to trap Red John, and it worked.
Jane is with him right now,
and his life is in grave danger.
He's at 5071 Keston Avenue.
Uh-huh.
(Grunts) That's enough.
We haven't got much time.
Put him
in the passenger seat.
(Grunting)
(Continues grunting)
(Breathing heavily)
(Red John) Hello, Patrick.
Hey.
How you doing?
Debonair at all costs, huh?
When did you know?
Oh, you strung me along
for a good long while.
Well done.
Luckily, I have a good friend
in the FBI,
so I found out
when the FBI found out.
Cat got your tongue?
I have nothing to say.
Really? Nothing?
"Go to hell"
goes without saying,
so, yes, nothing.
As you well know, Patrick,
there is no hell.
When I die, I won't be punished.
What if you really did have
a change of heart?
What if you and I were friends?
Imagine the life we could lead.
It's a higher path, Patrick.
A nobler existence.
Like I said, go to hell.
Oh, well, as you wish.
Lorelei, cut off
two of his fingers.
You choose which.
Then we should go.
(Grunting)
Aah!
I'm sorry.
Aah! Aah!
(Siren whoops)
Aah!
(Siren wailing)
(Tires screech)
FBI! Turn off the vehicle!
Let me see your hands!
Get your hands up!
(Error tone chimes)
(Female automated voice) This
call has been disconnected.
Please hang up
and try your call again.
(Mouths word)
(Car doors close)
You all right?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Never better.
(Siren wailing in distance)
I'm very happy
to meet you, Lorelei.
We rarely get
the chance to talk
to someone who knows
Red John so well.
Good to meet you, too.
Heard so much about you.
We were lovers, him and me.
Did he tell you that?
No?
Why not, lover?
Are you ashamed of me?
Did we do something bad?
I know it's hard
to believe now,
but you're gonna talk to us.
You're gonna break down,
and you're gonna tell us
everything you know
about Red John.
You're gonna sing
like a bird.
No, lover.
I won't.
Yes, you will.
(Kisses)
(Whispers)
Yes, you will.
(Door closes)
An exclusive of web proposed
by " Benjo The Masked Robber ".
www.tvsubtitles.net